Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6337
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements
1941- 2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seyfarth Shaw LLP
6337
17 cubic feet
17 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
Photocopies of collective bargaining agreements (CBAs). Unions strongly represented include AFSCME, Laborers, Operating Engineers, Police unions, SEIU, and the Teamsters. The geographic focus of the collection is the state of Illinois. Cook County and the Chicago, IL area are well represented, as is Springfield and a few other areas in the southern part of the state.
7655797
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 20, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection consists collective bargaining agreements (CBAs). Virtually all the CBAs in the collection are photocopies. Most strongly represented in the collection are AFSCME, Laborers, Operating Engineers, Police unions, SEIU, and the Teamsters. The geographic focus of the collection is the state of Illinois. Cook County and the Chicago, IL area are well represented, as is Springfield and a few other areas in the southern part of the state.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6336: Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Union Documents 6346 PUBS: Seyfarth Shaw Labor Publications 6350: Seyfarth Shaw Newsclipping File
Collective labor agreements.; AFSCME; Service Employees International Union; Seyfarth Shaw LLP; Teamsters
7655797
- AFSCME Council 31, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Springfield, IL
- AFSCME Local 337, 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AFSCME Local 473, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  County of Winnebago, IL
- AFSCME Local 759, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Caton, IL
- AFSCME Local 807, 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Joliet, IL
- AFSCME Local 909, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Streamwood, IL
- AFSCME Local 964, 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Villa Park, IL
- AFSCME Local 928B, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Ottawa, IL
- AFSCME Local 1331, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Urbana, IL
- AFSCME Local 2837, 1982-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Waukegan, IL
- AFSCME Local 2961, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Will County, IL
- AFSCME Local 3189, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- AFSCME Local 3369, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  County of Williamson, IL
- UAW Local 2282, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Moline, IL
- Belvidere City Employees Association, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Belvidere, IL
- Building and Construction Trades Craftsmen, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Kankakee, IL
- Building Trades Coalition, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Chicago, IL
- Clerical/Technical Employee Group, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Elgin, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Bellwood, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1983-1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Des Plaines, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Evanston, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Evergreen Park, IL
- Combined Counties Police association, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Maywood, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Oak Lawn, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  River Forest, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Romeoville, IL
- Combined Counties Police Association, 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Wheeling, IL
- Communications Workers of America, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  North Chicago, IL
- Fraternal Order of Policy Labor Council, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Forest Park, IL
- Hanover Park Patrol Officers Association (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Hanover Park, IL
- IBEW Local 9, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- IBEW Local 193, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- IBEW Local 196, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Batavia, IL
- IBEW Local 196, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Naperville, IL
- IBEW Local 196, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  St. Charles, IL
- IBEW Local 702, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Southern Illinois University
- Illinois Municipal Policy Association, 1984-1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Berwyn, IL
- Illinois Nurses Association, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Illinois Nurses Association Illinois Department of Central Management Services (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Industrial Workers Union Local 300 Citizens Utilities Company, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Laborers International Union Local 160, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Murphysboro, IL
- Laborers International Union Local 198, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Saling County, IL
- Laborers International Union Local 253, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Jacksonville, IL
- Laborers Internaitonal Union Local 477, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Laborers International Union Local 529, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Lefferson County, IL
- Laborers International Union Local 644, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Perry County, IL
- Laborers International Union Local 793 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Johnson County, IL
- Laborers International Union Local 1001, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Bartlett, IL
- Laborers International Union Local 1001, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Laborers International Union Local 1002, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- IAM Local 701, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Oak Park, IL
- IAM Local 1000, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Bloomington, IL
- IAM Local 1815, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Bolingbrook, IL
- Metropolitan Aliiance of Police Chapter 15, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Crest Hill, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 18, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Bridgeview, IL
- Metropolitan Aliiance of Police Chapter 24, 1988-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Metropolitan Aliiance of Police Chapter 27, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Metropolitan Aliiance of Police Chapter 36 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Crete, IL
- Metropolitan Aliiance of Police Chapter 48, 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Darien, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 51, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Woodbridge, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 54 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Winnetka, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 60, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Justice, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 63, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Morris, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 75, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Lockport, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 78, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Algonquin, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 84, 1987-1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Mount Prospect, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 93, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Plainfield, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 129, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Wilmington, IL
- Metropolitan Alliance of Police Chapter 150, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Palos Park, IL
- Operation Engineers Local 7, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Operating Engineers Local 7, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Operating Engineers Local 150, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Palatine, IL
- Operating Engineers Local 310, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Metropolis, IL
- Operating Engineers Local 318, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Union County, IL
- Operating Engineers Local 318, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  Williamson County, IL
- Operating Engineering Local 339, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  Bourbonnas, IL
- Operating Engineers Local 399, 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Operating Engineers Local 525, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Highland, IL
- Operating Engineers Local 965, 965A, 965B, 965C, 965RA, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Painters and Allied Trades Local 99, 1983-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Public Services Employee Group, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Saint Charles Patrolmen's Association, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- SEIU Local 1 Division 11, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- SEIU Local 1, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Park Rider, IL
- SEIU Local 11, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- SEIU Local 46 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Chicago Park District, Chicago, IL
- SEIU Local 46, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Cook County, IL
- SEIU Local 73 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- SEIU Local 73, 1984-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Office of the Secretary of State (Illinois)
- SEIU District 925, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- SEIU District 925, 1983-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Schaumberg Public Workers Employees Advisory Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Schaumberg, IL
- Springfield Graphic Communications Union Local 30C, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Teamsters Local 26, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Edgar County, IL
- Teamsters Local 330, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Teamsters Local 347, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Shawnee Library System
- Teamsters Local 423, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Aurora Sanitary District, IL
- Teamsters Local 435, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Whiteside County, IL
- Teamsters Local 525 Madison County, IL, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Teamsters Local 525, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Nameori, IL
- Teamsters Local 627, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Peoria, IL
- Teamsters Local 705, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Teamsters Local 705 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Teamsters Local 705, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Thorn Creek Basin Sanitary District, IL
- Teamsters Local 714, 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Teamsters Local 714, 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Hinsdale, IL
- Teamsters Local 714, 1988-1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Hoffman Estates, IL
- Teamsters Local 714, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Willowbrook, IL
- Teamsters Local 714, 1991-1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Western Springs, IL
- Teamsters Local 714, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  Wood Dale, IL
- Teamsters Local 726, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Calumet City, IL
- Teamsters Local 726, 1984-1995 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Teamsters Local 726, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Country Club Hills, IL
- Teamsters Local 726, 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Glendale Heights, IL
- Teamsters Local 726, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Glenwood, IL
- Teamsters Local 726, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Homewood, IL
- Teamsters Local 726, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  Markham, IL
- Teamsters Local 726, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Oak Forest, IL
- Teamsters Local 916, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Teamsters Local 916, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Wheeling Operations and Maintenance Department Non- Supervisory Employees Association, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Wheeling Police Department Employees Association, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Alpha, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Auto Mechanics, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- United Auto Workers, 1979-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- UAW/Chrysler, 1981-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- UAW/Chrysler, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- United Auto Workers (D-E), 1982-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- UAW/Ford, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- UAW/Ford, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- UAW/Ford, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- UAW/Ford, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- UAW/Ford, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- UAW/Ford, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- UAW/Ford, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- UAW/Ford, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- UAW/Ford, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- UAW/Franklin Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- UAW/General Motors, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- UAW/General Motors, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- UAW/General Motors, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- UAW/General Motors, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- UAW/General Motors, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- UAW/General Motors, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- UAW/General Motors, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- UAW/General Motors, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- UAW/General Motors, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- UAW/General Motors, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- UAW/General Motors, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- UAW/General Motors, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- UAW/General Motors, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- UAW/General Motors, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- UAW/General Motors, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- UAW/General Motors, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- UAW/General Motors, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- UAW/General Motors, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- UAW/General Motors, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- UAW/General Motors, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- UAW/General Motors, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- UAW/General Motors, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- UAW/International Harvester, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- UAW/International Harvester, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- UAW/International Harvester, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- UAW/H-K, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- UAW/Insurance Program, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- UAW/Morse Industrial, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- UAW/New United Motor Manufacturing, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- UAW/New United Motor Manufacturing, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- UAW/Porter, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- UAW/Saturn Motors, 1985-2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- UAW/Strong Electric, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- UAW/Suntec Industries, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- UAW/Thompson-Smith, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- UAW/Walker Manufacturing, 1980-1991 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- UAW Special Collective Bargaining Convention (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Automotive, Petroleum, and Allied Industries Employees Union, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Bakery, Confectionary, and Tobacco Workers, 1976-1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Boilermakers, 1967-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Book Binders, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers, 1975-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1973-1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Builders Association of Chicago, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Carpenters, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Carpenters, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Carpenters, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Carpenters, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Carpenters Pension Plans, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Cement, Lime, and Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1937-1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Cement, Lime, Gypsum and Allied Workers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Clinical Workers, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Chicago Truck Drivers, 1976-1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Clothing and Textile Workers of America (ACWA) Pension Plans, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Communication Workers of America, 1949-1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- "C" Miscellaneous, 1980-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Die Stinkers Union, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Distributive Workers Pension Materials, 1950-1958 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- IUE (A-G), 1969-2007 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- IUE (H-Z), 1950-1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- IUE (Pension Material), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Works (A-I), 1970-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- IBEW, 1976-1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Electric and Space Technicians- Contracts, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- "E" Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- United Food and Commercial Workers (A-H), 1971-2004 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- UFCW (I-Z), 1979-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- UFCW (Pension Materials; Merger Agreement), 1976-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Furniture Workers, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- "F" Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of General Workers, 1977-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- United Glass and Ceramic Workers Union, 1979-1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- American Flint Glass Workers Union, 1948-1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Graphic Art International Union, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Graphic Communications (Pension Materials), 1986-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Hospital Employees, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Hotel & Restaurant Employees International Union, 1969-1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- "H" Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 12)
- "J" Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Laborers' International Union, 1967-1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Laborers' International Union (Pension Materials), 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- International Ladies Garment Workers, 1966-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Laundry Workers, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Chicago Lithographers Association, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- International Longshoremen's Association, 1957-1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- "L" Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Machinery Workers, 1973-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- International Association of Machinists, 1971-1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- International Association of Machinists, 1960-1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Meat Cutters, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Metal Processor's Union, 1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Midwest Pension Plan, 1967-1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Milk Drivers Union, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Mine Workers, 1974-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- International Molders and Allied Workers Union, 1976-1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Musicians Union, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- "M' Miscellaneous, 1981-1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- National Industrial Group Pension Plan (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Newspaper Guild, 1976-1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Nurses Association, 1978-1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- "N" Miscellaneous, 1967-1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Office and Professional Employees, 1971-2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers, 1961-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers Pension Fund, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- International Union of Operating Engineers, 1957-1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Operating Engineers (Pension Material), 1977-1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, 1979-2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- "O" Miscellaneous, 1979-2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Packinghouse, Food and Allied Workers, 1961-1964 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Allied Painters Union, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- United Paperworkers International Union, 1967-1998 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Plasters' Union, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Service Employees- International Union, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Service Employees- International Union, 1982-2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Fraternal Order of Police, 1981-1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Printing and Graphic Communication Union, 1973-1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- "D" Miscellaneous, 1968-1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Railway Workers, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Retail Clerks Union, 1971-1980 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Retail Workers Pension & Benefits Material, 1973-1981 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Rockford Education Association, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- United Rubber Workers/ G-L, 1944-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- United Rubber Workers/ M-T, 1941-1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- United Rubber Workers/ U-W, 1974-1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Saturn Motors and NUMMI Developments, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Saturn Motors and NUMMI Developments, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- SEIU, 1969-2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- SEIU, 1969-2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- SEIU, 1969-2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Sheet Metal Workers, 1972-1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- AFSCME/ A-D, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- AFSCME/ E-M, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- AFSCME/ N-R, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- AFSCME/ S-W, 1976-1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- AFSCME, 1979-1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Independent Steel Workers Alliance, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- USWA Basic, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- USWA Basic, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- USWA Basic, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- USWA Basic, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- USWA/ACF Industries, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- USWA/ Allegheny Ludlum Industries, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- USWA/ Aluminum Company of America (ALCOA), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- USWA/ American Can, 1971-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- USWA/ United Steel Workers of America, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- USAW/ Bethlehem Steel, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- USWA/ Bethlehem Steel, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- USAW/ Bethlehem Steel, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- USWA/ Bethlehem Steel, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- USWA/ Bethlehem Steel, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- USWA/ B, 1977-1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- USWA/ Can Industry, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- USWA/ Coordinating Committee Steel Companies, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- USWA/ Coordinating Committee Steel Companies, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- USWA/ Coordinating Committee Steel Companies, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- USWA/ Crucible, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- USWA/ D, 1978-1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- USWA/ Howmet Turbine Components, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- USWA/ Inland Steel, 1956-1962 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- USWA/ Inland Steel, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- USWA/ Inland Steel, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- USWA/ Inland Steel, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- USWA/ Ispat Inland, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- USWA/ LTV Steel, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- USWA/ L, 1976-1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- USWA/ M, 1978-1994 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- USWA/ National Steel, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- USWA/ Northwestern Steel and Wire, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- USWA/ P, 1975-1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- USWA/ Roblin Steel, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- USWA/ Schlitz, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- USWA/ Shenango China, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- USWA/ United States Steel, 1962-1971 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- USWA/ United States Steel, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- USWA/ United States Steel, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- USWA/ United States Steel, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- USWA/ USX, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- USWA/ USX, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- USWA/ USX, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- USWA/ USX, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- USWA/ USX, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- USWA Proposed Agreements, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- USWA Proposed Agreements, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- USWA Proposed Agreements, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- USWA Pension Agreements, 1969-1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- USWA Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, 1956-1977 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- "S" Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Teachers, 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Teachers, 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Teachers, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Teachers, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Teamsters, Local Union 1-100, 1976-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, Local Union 101-200, 1976-2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Teamsters, Local Union 201-300, 1993-1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Teamsters, Local Union 301-400, 1974-1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Teamsters, Local Union 401-500, 1971-2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Teamsters, Local Union 501-600, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Teamsters, Local Union 601-700, 1976-1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Teamsters, Local Union 701-999, 1977-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Teamsters, Local Union 705, 1979-1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Teamsters Local Union 710, 1976-1986 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Teamsters Local Union 714, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Teamsters Local Union 761, 1970-1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Teamsters Local Union 781, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 1991-1998 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Teamsters National Master Freight Agreement, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Teamsters General, 1973-1997 (Box 17, Folder 13)